# Zeinab Kamel Kamal

- Morog Al Amir, near Tabuk Park , Tabuk
- 0534409464
- ⊠ Zeinabkamel2011@gmail.com

#### Education

Bachelor of Education, Assiut university, Egypt.

**Grade: Very Good** 

#### Personal Skills

Working Knowledge

Ability to Develop

Creative

• • • • • • •

Problem Solving

• • • • • •

Graphics Software Knowledge

# **Hobbies**







# Languages

Arabic:



## **Professional Summary**

Energetic, Self-motivated, Excellent communicator, Frequently worked on large teams & Creative designer with over 10 years of experience in creating all pharmaceutical packaging materials and professional promotional materials (flyers – brochures – business cards – infographics, advertisements - mockup.... etc.) while helping clients cut costs by an average of 10%, seeking for an opportunity of the desired position as a remote graphic designer.

#### **Work Experiences**

<u>2013 - 2022:</u> Packaging materials and promotion media Designer for (Servier Egypt Industries Limited – pharmed healthcare – Riva pharma - SAJA pharmaceuticals Egypt).

<u>2006 - 2013:</u> Packaging materials Designer at UP pharma (T3A industrial previously).

2004 - 2006: graphics designer at advertising company.

# **Duties and Responsibilities**

- \* Creating Corporate Visual Identity Designs for the organization including (brochures, flayers, business cards, letterhead, envelopes......).
- \* Creating all pharmaceutical packaging material designs (outer pack, inner label, aluminum foil, tube & insert) using all support graphics design software.
- \* Coordinate with all Departments (R.A, Q.C, Q.A & Supply chain) to get all data related to packaging materials layouts (Dimensions, colors & approved scientific data...) and take final approval on finished layouts.
- \* Contact printing houses to make sure that the printing procedures go normally and to solve any technical problems related to sent layouts.
- \* Update the layouts according to any variation from any department with a new different issue No.

## **Training Courses**

(2003) Basic business skills Acquisition- from Future Generation Foundation

(2004) Computer course (Microsoft Office)- from Ministry of defense

(2006) Business soft skills program-from YAT education centers

(2006) English course-from The American university in Cairo Advanced interpersonal communication.

Effective presentation, Business problem solving, Strategic decision making, Excellence in service, Sales skills-basic. (2006) Graphics & multimedia design and development- from YAT education centers

- Adobe acrobat 7.0 fundamentals
- XHTML & CSS fundamentals
- Adobe Photoshop CS2
- Adobe Illustrator CS2
- AutoCAD 2006 Essentials
- Macromedia flash 8
- Macromedia Dreamweaver 8
- 3ds max 8 essentials 3ds max design visualization
- Character studio 4 fundamentals
- Adobe InDesign CS2
- MAX Script Development
- Combustion 4
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Macromedia Director MX 2004 & Lingo
- Software integration
- Print to video
- Implementing PM using MS-Project 2003

(2013) Graphics diploma in Russian culture center containing:

- Adobe Photo shop CC
- Adobe illustrator CC
- Adobe in design CC
- Adobe After effect CC

## **Awards and Certifications**

- Adobe certified expert in Photoshop CS2- from Adobe systems. incorporated.
- Certified Macromedia Flash MX 2004 Designer- from Adobe systems incorporated.
- Autodesk 3ds max 8- from Autodesk.
- International Computer Driving License (ICDL)- from UNESCO & Ministry of communications and information technology.